邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural.
那晚发生的事
What happened that night.
赶快把你弟弟带到外面去
Take your brother outside as fast as you can!
快 迪恩 快跑
Now Dean! Go!
他们亲眼目睹
What they witnessed.
玛丽 不
Mary! No!
两兄弟
Sent two brothers.
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
从此踏上征途 22年后
On a quest for answers. 22 years later.
我发过誓我再也不猎魔了
I swore I was done hunting,
我一个人干不了
I can't do this alone.
不
No!
我们有活儿干了
We got work to do.
这是爸爸唯一的
This is dad's single.
最有价值的东西
most valuable possession.
他所知道的关于恶魔的东西都记载在这里面
Everything he knows about every evil thing is in here.
我觉得他想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
你知道 拯救人类
You know, saving people,
猎杀恶魔
hunting things…
家族事业
Family business.
不
No.
我得找出杀杰西卡的凶手
I gotta find Jessica's killer.
这是我现在唯一想做的事
It's the only thing I can think about.
萨姆 你知道我们会找到爸爸的 是吧
Sam, you know we're gonna find Dad, right?
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.
《邪恶力量》
（威斯康辛州 曼莱托克湖）
早安 爸爸
Morning, daddy.
早安 甜心
Morning, sweetheart.
你做的这些健身 索菲 我说不好
All these workouts, Soph, I don't know.
男生不喜欢壮硕的女生
Guys don't like buff girls.
不过女生也不喜欢还住父母家的男生
Yeah, well, girls don't like guys who still live at home.
小心点
Be careful.
我会的
I will.
还需要什么吗
Can I get you anything else?
请结帐
Just the check, please.
好吧
Okay.
萨姆 我们可以偶尔找点乐子
You know, Sam, we are allowed to have fun once in a while.
那就是乐子
That's fun.
这儿 看这个 我想我找到了一个
Here, take a look at this. I think I got one.
威斯康辛州 曼莱托克湖
Lake Manitoc, Wisconsin.
上周 索菲·卡尔顿
Last week, Sophie Carlton,
18岁 下水之后
18, walks into the lake,
就再也没起来
doesn't walk out.
当局彻底搜索了整个水域
Authorities dragged the water.
什么也没找到
Nothing.
索菲·卡尔顿
Sophie Carlton.
是今年曼莱托克湖淹死的第三个人了
is the third Lake Manitoc drowning this year.
其他人的尸体也都没找到
None of the other bodies were found, either.
两天前他们举行了葬礼
They had a funeral two days ago.
葬礼
A funeral?
是的 他们埋了一具空棺材
Yes, they buried an empty coffin.
作个了结之类的
for closure or whatever.
了结
Closure?
什么样的了结
What closure?
那些人不是简单的失踪 迪恩
People don't just disappear, Dean.
人们却停止了寻找
Other people just stop looking for them.
你想跟我说什么
Something you want to say to me?
爸爸的踪迹 最近都没音信
The trail for dad. It's getting colder every day.
- 那我们该怎么办 - 不知道
- What are we supposed to do? - I don't know.
总得做点事
Something.
- 任何事 - 你知道吗
- Anything. - You konw what.
我受够了你这种态度
I'm sick of this attitude.
你以为我不像你一样想找到爸爸吗
You don't think I want to find dad as much as you do?
是 我知道你也想
Yeah, I know you do it.
在过去两年里
I'm the one that's been with.
是我每一天都陪在爸爸身边
him every single day for the past two years.
那时你却在大学里开赛前动员会
While you've been off to college going to pep rallies.
我们会找到爸爸的
We will find dad,
但在此之前 我们必须消灭这一路上
but until then, we're gonna kill everything bad,
所有的恶魔
between here and there.
明白吗
Okay?
好吧 曼莱托克湖
All right, Lake Manitoc.
离这多远
How far?
（欢迎来到曼莱托克湖）
威尔·卡尔顿吗
Will Carlton?
对 是我
Yeah, that's right.
我是探员福特
I'm agent Ford.
这是探员哈迈尔
This is agent Hamill.
我们是美国野生动物管理局的
We're with the U.S. Wild Life Service.
她大概游了100码远
She was about 100 yards out.
那就是她被拖下水的地方
That's where she got dragged down.
你确定她不是溺水吗
And you're sure she didn't just drown?
是的 她是学校的游泳健将
Yeah. She was a varsity swimmer.
她几乎在那个湖里长大
She practically grew up in that lake.
她在那儿就像在自己的浴缸里一样安全
She's as safe out there as in her own bathtub.
那么没有水花
So no splashing,
没有因为痛苦自杀的迹象
no signs of distress?
没有 就跟我说的一样
No, that's what I'm telling you.
你看见水里有影子吗
Did you see any shadows in the water,
也许
maybe,
有个黑色的东西跃出水面
some dark shape breach the surface?
没有 再说一遍 她当时离得太远了
No, again, she was really far out there.
你没在岸边看见什么奇怪的东西吗
You ever see any strange tracks by the shoreline?
没 绝对没有
No, never.
为什么这么问
Why?
会有什么东西在那儿
What do you think's out there?
我们一查清楚就告诉你
We'll let you know as soon as we do.
你爸爸呢
What about your father?
我们能和他谈谈吗
Can we talk to him?
听着 如果你们不介意的话
Look, If you don't mind, I mean,
他什么也没看到 而且他很痛苦
He didn't see anything, and he's kind of been through a lot.
我们能理解
We understand.
无意冒犯 但是
Now, I'm sorry, but,
怎么野生动物管理局对意外溺水案有兴趣了
why does the Wildlife Service care about an accidental drowning?
你确定是意外吗
You sure it's accidental?
威尔·卡尔顿看见有东西抓住了他姐姐
Will Carlton saw something grab his sister.
什么东西
Like what?
来 请坐
Here, sit, please.
湖里没有任何本地生的肉食动物
There are no indigenous carnivores in that lake.
甚至没有大到能拖人下水的生物
There's nothing even big enough to pull down a person,
除非是尼斯湖水怪
unless it was the Loch Ness monster.
是的
Yeah, right.
威尔·卡尔顿伤心欲绝
Will Carlton was traumatized,
而且有时候 人的思维是会捉弄人的
and sometimes the mind plays tricks.
再者
Still,
为进一步确定 我们彻底搜索了整个湖
we dragged that entire lake. We even ran a sonar sweep,
还做了声纳扫描 但是什么都没找到
just to be sure, and there was nothing down there.
真是诡异
That's weird, though.
这可是今年失踪的第三具尸体了
That's the third missing body this year.
我知道
I know.
他们都是我镇上的人
These are people from my town.
都是我该照顾的人
These are people I care about.
我明白
I know.
无论如何
Anyway...
所有这一切
All this.
不会再成问题了
It won't be a problem much longer.
什么意思
What do you mean?
当然是水坝啊
Well, the dam, of course.
当然
Of course.
水坝
The dam.
它…
It's, uh…
它漏水了
It sprung a leak.
它要塌了
It's falling apart,
而且政府不愿给我们资金去维修
and the feds won't give us the grant to repair it,
所以他们开出了一条泄洪道
so they've opened the spillway.
再过六个月
In another six months,
湖就不存在了
there won't be much of a lake.
这个镇子也将不存在了
There won't be much of a town, either,
不过作为野生动物管理局人员
but as federal wildlife,
你们应该早就知道了
you already knew that.
没错
Exactly.
不好意思 我打扰你们了吗
Sorry, am I interrupting?
我还是等会再来吧
I think come back later.
先生们 这是我女儿
Gentlemen, this is my daughter.
很高兴认识你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
我是迪恩
I'm Dean.
安德里亚·巴尔 你好
Andrea Barrr. Hi.
你好
Hi.
他们是野生动物管理局的
They're from the wildlife service,
来调查有关湖的事情
about the lake.
你好啊
Oh, hey, there.
叫什么名字
What's your name?
他叫卢卡斯
His name is Lucas.
他还好吗
Is he okay?
我外孙最近经历了太多事情
My grandson's been through a lot.
我们都经历了很多
We all have.
好吧
Well,
如果有什么事我能帮上忙
if there's anything else I can do for you,
跟我说就行
please, let me know.
谢谢
Thanks.
既然你这样说了
You know, now that you mentioned it,
我想打听一下
could you point us in the.
附近有价钱公道的旅店吗
direction of a reasonably priced motel?
湖滨汽车旅馆
Lakefront motel, go around the corner,
过两个街区就到了
it's two blocks up.
两个街区
Two.
可以带我们过去吗
Would you mind showing us?
你想让我陪你们走两个街区
You want me to walk you two blocks?
如果不麻烦的话
Not if it's any trouble.
反正我也往那个方向走
I'm headed that way anyway.
我三点回来接卢卡斯
I'll be back to pick up lucas at 3:00.
宝贝 我们等会去公园好吗
We'll go to the park, okay, sweetie?
多谢
Thanks again.
孩子很可爱
So, cute kid.
谢谢
Thanks.
孩子是最可爱的 对吧
Kids are the best, huh?
到了
There it is.
就像我说的 两个街区
Like I said, two blocks.
谢谢
Thanks.
你方向感这么差 一定老碰壁吧
Must be hard with your sense of direction,
都想不出一句搭讪的好词儿
never being able to find your way to a decent pickup line.
希望你们过得愉快
Enjoy your stay.
「孩子是最可爱的」
"Kids are the best"?
- 你根本不喜欢小孩 - 我喜欢
- You don't even like kids. - I love kids.
说出三个你认识的小孩名字
Name three children that you even know.
我在想呢
I'm thinking.
今年有三名溺水者
So there's the three drowning victims this year.
之前呢
And before that?
还有6个
Yeah, six more,
在过去35年里
spread outover the past 35 years.
那些尸体也都消失了
Those bodies were never recovered, either.
如果湖里有东西
If there is something out there,
那它正在加快厮杀速度
it's picking up its pace.
这么说 就是有个湖怪在为非作歹
So we got a lake monster on a binge?
我觉得这湖怪理论有点不对劲
This whole lake monster theory, it just bugs me.
为什么
Why?
尼斯湖 恰普伦湖
Loch Ness, lake Champlain.
都有成百上千的目击者
there are literally hundreds of eyewitness accounts,
但在这儿 没有任何目击者
but here, almost nothing.
不管那是什么东西
Whatever it is out there,
没人说的出来
No one's living to talk about it.
等等 巴尔
Wait, Barr,
克里斯多佛·巴尔 我听过这个名字
Christopher Barr, where have I heard that name before?
克里斯多佛·巴尔 五月份的受害者
Christopher Barr, the victim in may.
克里斯多佛·巴尔是安德里亚的丈夫
Christopher Barr was Andrea's husband,
卢卡斯的爸爸
Lucas' father.
据报道
Apparently,
他带卢卡斯去游泳
he took Lucas out swimming.
克里斯溺水时 卢卡斯在一块浮木上
Lucas was on a floating wooden platform when Chris drowned,
两小时后
2 hours,
孩子才被救起
before the kid got rescued.
也许我们终于找到一名目击者了
Maybe we have an eyewitness after all.
难怪那孩子如此恐惧
No wonder that kid was so freaked out.
亲眼见到父亲或母亲死亡
Watching one of your.
可不是那么容易忘怀的
parents die isn't something you just get over.
我能陪陪你吗
Can we join you?
我在陪我儿子
I'm here with my son.
我能跟他打个招呼吗
Mind if I say hi?
告诉你朋友
Tell your friend this whole.
这套「甜心先生」的把戏 对我不管用
"Jerry maguire" Thing's not gonna work on me.
我想他没那意思
I don't think that's what this is about.
画得怎么样啦
How's it going?
我以前也爱玩这些
Oh, I used to love these things.
看来你更喜欢蜡笔画
So crayons is more your thing?
很酷 小妞们都喜欢艺术家
That's cool. Chicks dig artists.
画得不错
Hey, these are pretty good.
我可以坐下来陪你画一会吗
You mind if I sit and draw with you for a while?
我画画也不赖
I'm not so bad myself.
我知道你在听我说话
You know, I'm thinking you can hear me.
你只是不想说话
You just don't want to talk.
我不知道你爸爸到底经历了什么
I don't know exactly what happened to your dad,
但是我知道 那肯定很可怕
but I know it was something real bad.
我想我了解你的感受
I think I know how you feel.
我像你这么大时 也看到了一些东西
When I was your age, I saw something.
不管怎样
Anyway...
也许你觉得没人会听你说
Maybe you don't think anyone will listen to you.
或者
Or, uh…
或者相信你
Or believe you.
我想让你知道 我会
I want you to know that I will.
你什么都不用说
You don't even have to.
给我画幅画就好了
say anything. You could draw me a picture,
画出那天到底发生了什么
about what you saw that day,
在你爸爸身上
with your dad,
在湖上发生的
on the lake.
好吧
Okay,
没关系
no problem.
这个送给你
This is for you.
这是我的家人
This is my family.
这是我爸爸
That's my dad.
那是
That's…
那是我妈妈
That's my mom.
这是我的怪人老弟
That's my geek brother,
这个是我
and that's me.
好吧 我是个很烂的画家
All right, so I'm a sucky artist.
再见 卢卡斯
I'll see you around, Lucas.
自从他爸出事以后
Lucas hasn't said a word, not even to me,
卢卡斯一言不发 跟我也一样
not since his dad's accident.
是的 我们听说了
Yeah, we heard.
很抱歉
Sorry.
医生怎么说
What are the doctors saying?
精神创伤后遗症
That it's a kind of post-traumatic stress.
那一定不容易
That can't be easy.
对你们两个来说
for either of you.
我们搬去了我爸家
We moved in with my dad.
他帮了我们很多
He helps out a lot.
只是
It's just…
每当我想到卢卡斯所遭遇的
when I think about what Lucas went through,
所看见的
what he saw…
小孩子其实很坚强
Kids are strong.
你一定会惊讶 他们能应对这些事儿
You'd be surprised what they can deal with.
你知道 他过去就是那样
You know, he used to have such life.
跟你说真的 以前很难和他相处
He was hard to keep up with, to tell you the truth.
现在他就坐在那
Now he just sits there,
画画 和玩具兵一起游戏
drawing those pictures, playing with those army men.
我只是希望
I just wish.
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你 卢卡斯
Thanks, Lucas.
爸爸
Hey, dad.
你该吃点东西了
You should probably eat something.
我去做晚饭 好吗
I'm gonna make some dinner, okay?
那么
So,
应该可以排除水怪的可能性了
I think it's safe to say we can rule out Nessie.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我刚开车经过卡尔顿家
I just drove past the Carlton house.
那有辆救护车
There was an ambulance there.
威尔·卡尔顿死了
Will Carlton is dead.
淹死了
He drowned?
是的 淹死在水槽里
Yep, in the sink.
这他妈怎么回事
What the hell?
那么你是对的 这不是个生物
So this isn't a creature.
我们在对付另外一种东西
We're dealing with something else.
对 但是什么东西
Yeah, but what?
不知道
I don't know.
也许是个水鬼
A water wraith maybe?
某种恶魔
Some kind of demon?
我是说 某种能控制水的东西
I mean, something that controls water…
能控制从同一个源头来的水
…Water that comes from the Same source.
- 那个湖 - 对
- The lake - Yeah.
这就能解释为何它要加快杀人的速度
which would explain why it's upping the body count.
湖水过几个月就会流干
The lake is draining.It'll be dry in a few months.
不管它是什么东西
Whatever this thing is,
也不管它想怎样
whatever it wants,
它就快没时间了
it's running out of time.
如果它能通过管道
And if it can get through the pipes,
它就能找到任何人
it can get to anyone,
到达任何地方
almost anywhere.
悲剧将会很快重演
This is gonna happen again soon.
而且我们还确定
And we do know one other thing for sure.
这事一定和比尔·卡尔顿有关
We know this has got something to do with Bill Carlton.
它杀了他的两个孩子
It took both his kids.
我问了附近的人
And I've been asking around.
卢卡斯的爸爸克里斯
Lucas' dad, Chris.
是比尔·卡尔顿的教子
Bill Carlton's godson.
我们去拜访一下卡尔顿先生
Let's go pay Mr. Carlton a visit.
卡尔顿先生
Mr. Carlton?
能问你几个问题吗
We'd like to ask you a few questions,
如果你不介意的话
if you don't mind.
我们是野生动物管理局
We're from the department.
我无所谓你们从哪儿来
I don't care who you're with.
我今天回答的问题够多了
I've answered enough questions today.
你儿子说他看见湖里有东西
Your son said he saw something in that lake.
你呢
What about you?
你看见过什么东西吗
You ever see anything out there?
卡尔顿先生
Mr. Carlton,
索菲的溺水和威尔的死
Sophie's drowning and Will's death.
我们觉得或许
We think there might be a connection,
跟你或你们家有关系
to you or your family.
我孩子都走了
My children are gone.
这
It's…
我生不如死
It's worse than dying.
快走吧
Go away…
拜托了
Please.
你怎么想
What do you think?
我觉得这个可怜的人受尽了折磨
I think the poor guy's been through hell.
我还觉得他有所隐瞒
I also think he's not telling us something.
那现在怎么办
So now what?
怎么了
What is it?
也许比尔不是唯一知道真相的人
Maybe Bill's not the only one who knows something.
抱歉 我觉得这不合适
I'm sorry, but I don't think it's a good idea.
我必须得跟他谈谈
I just need to talk to him,
几分钟就好
just for a few minutes.
他什么都不会说的
He won't say anything.
- 这么做有什么好处 - 安德里亚
- What good's it gonna do? - Andrea,
我们认为 更多的人将被害
we think more people might get hurt.
可怕的事还在继续
We think something's happening out there.
我丈夫 其他人 他们只是溺水了
My husband, the others, they just drowned.
就这样
That's all.
如果你真的那么认为
If that's what you really believe,
我们就走
then we'll go,
但如果你认为
but if you think there's even a possibility.
还有其他一丁点的可能性
that something else could be going on here,
请让我跟您儿子谈谈
please let me talk to your son.
卢卡斯
Hey, Lucas.
还记得我吗
You remember me?
我
You know, I, uh…
我想谢谢你上次为我画的画
I wanted to thank you for that last drawing…
但是
…But the thing is.
我需要你再帮我个忙
I need your help again.
你怎么会画出这个的
How did you know to draw this?
你当时预感到有不好的事情要发生吗
Did you know something bad was gonna happen?
也许你可以
Maybe you could.
点头摇头
nod yes or no.
来回答我
for me.
你害怕了
You're scared.
没事的
It's okay.
我理解
I understand.
我像你这么大时
See, when I was your age,
也看见在我妈妈身上发生的可怕的事
I saw something real bad happen to my mom,
我那时也很害怕
and I was scared, too.
我不想说话
I didn't feel like talking,
就像你这样
just like you,
但是我妈妈
but, see, my mom,
我知道她希望我勇敢点
I know she wanted me to be brave.
我每天都这么想
I think about that every day.
我尽量让自己变得更勇敢
And I do my best to be brave.
也许你爸爸
And maybe your dad.
也希望你勇敢起来
wants you to be brave, too.
谢谢你 卢卡斯
Thanks, Lucas.
安德里亚说孩子在爸爸爸死前
Andrea said the kid never drew like that.
没画过这样的画
till his dad died.
曾经有案例是这样 极度痛苦的经历
There are cases going through a traumatic experience.
导致当事人
could make certain people more.
能预知未来和通灵
sensitive to premonitions, psychic tendencies.
是不是卢卡斯已经感觉到它了呢
What if Lucas is tapping into it somehow?
下一个人溺水不过是时间问题了
It's only a matter of time before somebody else drowns,
如果你有头绪了 赶快说吧
so if you got a better lead, please.
好吧
All right.
我们得去找另一栋房子
We got another house to find.
光这个镇上就有不下千栋的黄色两层房子
There's about a thousand yellow two-stories in this county alone.
看这个教堂
See this church?
我打赌附近可没有一千栋这玩意
I bet there's less than a thousand of those around here.
大学生还觉得自己蛮聪明的
Oh, college boy thinks he's so smart.
你刚刚说的有关妈的事
You know, um… What you said about mom.
你以前从来没跟我讲过
You never told me that before.
没什么大不了的
It's no big deal.
老天 我们不会要来个拥抱吧
Oh, god, we're not gonna have to hug or anything, are we?
很抱歉打搅你 夫人
We're sorry to bother you, madam,
请问有一个小男孩曾住在这吗
but does a little boy live here by chance?
他也许戴着
He might wear.
一顶蓝色的棒球帽
a blue ball cap,
骑一辆红色的单车
has a red bicycle.
没有 先生
No, sir.
很久前就没住在这里了
Not for a very long time.
彼得失踪了35年了
Peter's been gone 35 years now.
警察从来没
The police never.
我也不知道发生了什么
I never had any idea what happened.
他就这么消失了
He just disappeared.
失去他
Losing him,
那 那让我生不如死
it's… It's worse than dying.
他是在这失踪的吗
Did he disappear from here,
我是说 在这栋房子里
I mean, from this house?
他本该
He was supposed to.
在放学后
ride his bike.
骑着他的单车
straight home.
径直回家
after school,
但他再也没出现过
and he never showed up.
彼得·斯威尼和比利·卡尔顿 1970年
"Peter Sweeney and Billy Carlton, 1970."
你带走了所有的东西
You've taken everything,
所有人
everyone.
我一无所有了
I've got nothing left.
我过去不明白
I didn't understand.
不相信
I didn't believe.
现在我知道了
Now I think I do.
我想我终于知道了你想要什么
I think I finally know what you want.
这个小男孩 彼得·斯威尼失踪了
Okay, this little boy, Peter Sweeney, vanishes,
所有的线索都跟比尔·卡尔顿有关
and this is all connected to Bill Carlton somehow.
比尔肯定隐瞒了什么
Bill sure as hell seems to be hiding something.
而且这个比尔 所有他爱的人
And Bill, the people he loves.
全都遭到惩罚
they're all getting punished.
那就是说比尔对彼得做了什么
So that Bill did something to Peter.
如果是比尔杀了他呢
What if Bill killed him?
彼得的灵魂一定很愤怒
Peter's spirit would be furious.
它想报仇 这有可能
It'd want revenge. It's possible.
卡尔顿先生
Mr. Carlton!
看那边
Hey. Check it out.
卡尔顿先生 快回来
Mr. Carlton! You need to come back!
离开那湖 快掉头
Come out of the water! Turn the boat around!
宝贝 怎么了
Baby, what's wrong?
萨姆 迪恩
Sam, Dean.
没想到你们会来
I didn't expect to see you here.
你们现在混得挺熟了啊
So now you're on a first-name basis.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我给你带来了晚餐
I brought you dinner.
对不起 甜心 我现在没时间
I'm sorry, sweetheart. I don't really have the time.
我听说比尔·卡尔顿的事了
I heard about Bill Carlton.
是真的吗 湖里真有什么东西吗
Is it true? Is something going on with the lake?
现在我们还不清楚事情的真相
Right now, we don't know what the truth is,
但我觉得你还是带卢卡斯回家比较好
but I think it might be better if you and lucas went on home.
卢卡斯 怎么了
Lucas, hey, what is it?
- 卢卡斯 - 卢卡斯
- Lucas. - Lucas.
卢卡斯 没事的 没事的
Lucas, it's okay. It's okay. Hey,
Lucas, it's okay. It's okay.
好吧 只是想确定一下 你们看见
Okay, just so I'm clear, you see…
有东西
something…
袭击了比尔的船
attack Bill's boat,
把比尔
sending Bill,
一个游泳健将
who is a very good swimmer, by the way,
拖到了湖里
into the drink,
然后你们再也没见他上来
and you never see him again?
是的 大概就这样
Yeah, that about sums it up.
我应该相信这些
And I'm supposed to believe this,
虽然我用声纳搜索了整个湖底
even though I've already sonar-swept that entire lake.
但你们的描述难以让人信服
and what you're describing is impossible.
而且你们根本不是野生动物管理局的
and you're not really Wildlife Service?
是吧
That's right,
我查过了
I checked.
局里从来没听说过你们俩
The department's never heard of you two.
是这样的
See?
- 我们可以解释 - 够了
- Now, we can explain that. - Enough,
拜托
please.
你们还没被抓起来的唯一原因
The only reason you're breathing free air.
就是比尔的一个邻居
is one of Bill's neighbors saw.
在你们之前看见了他驾船出去
him steering out that boat just before you did.
所以
So.
现在有几个选择
we have a couple of options here.
我以冒充政府官员的名义逮捕你们
I can arrest you for impersonating government officials.
把你们作为
and hold you as material.
比尔·卡尔顿失踪案的人证扣押起来
witnesses to Bill Carlton's disappearance,
或者
or.
我们就当今天走了霉运
we can chalk this all up to a bad day,
你们开车
you get into your car,
马上从这儿离开
you put this town in your rearview mirror,
永远也不要回来
and you don't ever darken my doorstep.
永远
again!
第二种选择听起来不错
Door number two sounds good.
要是我 也选这个
That's the one I'd pick.
宝贝
Baby…
这么晚了你在做什么
What are you doing up?
来吧 睡觉去吧
Come on, let's go to bed.
绿灯了
Green.
什么
What?
变绿灯了
Light's green.
到另一个州了
Ah, the interstate's the other way.
我知道
I know.
（密尔沃基州）
迪恩 这事儿已经结束了
But, Dean, this job, I think it's over.
我不这样认为
I'm not so sure.
如果是比尔谋杀了彼得·斯威尼
If bill murdered Peter Sweeney.
而彼得的灵魂也报了仇
and Peter's spirit got its revenge,
事情就了结了 他的灵魂也该安息了
case closed. The spirit should be at rest.
如果我们走了事情还没结束怎么办
All right, so what if we take off and this thing isn't done?
万一我们漏掉了什么
What if we missed something?
致使更多人受害怎么办
What if more people get hurt?
你为什么要那样想
But why would you think that?
因为卢卡斯太害怕了
Because Lucas was really scared.
这就是原因吗
That's what this is about?
确定那孩子没事之前我不想离开
I just don't want to leave town till I know the kid's okay.
你是谁
Who are you,
你对我哥哥做了什么
and what have you done with my brother?
闭嘴
Shut up.
你确定这么做吗
Are you sure about this?
夜深了 伙计
It's pretty late, man.
卢卡斯 卢卡斯
Lucas? Lucas!
卢卡斯
Lucas!
能告诉我吗
Can you tell me?
不
No.
这根本说不通
It doesn't make any sense.
我一定是疯了
I'm going crazy.
不 你不是
No, you're not.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what happened.
所有事
Everything.
我听见了
I heard…
我觉得我听见了
I thought I heard…
一个声音
there was this voice.
它说什么了
What did it say?
它说
It said.
它说 「来和我玩」
it said, "Come play with me."
到底怎么了
What's happening?
（相册：杰克 12岁）
你能认出照片里的这些孩子吗
Do you recognize the kids in these pictures?
什么
What?
我不全认得
No, I huh…
我知道这是我爸爸
I mean, except that's my dad right there.
他那时候
He must have been about.
大概12岁
12 in these pictures.
克里斯·巴尔的溺水
Chris Barr's drowning.
不仅只跟比尔·卡尔顿有关
the connection wasn't to Bill Carlton.
一定还跟治安官有关
It must have been to sheriff.
比尔和治安官
Bill and the sheriff,
他们肯定跟彼得的死有关
they were both involved with Peter.
关于克里斯的什么
What about Chris?
我爸爸 你们在说什么
My dad, what are you talking about?
卢卡斯
Lucas?
卢卡斯 怎么了
Lucas, what is it?
卢卡斯 亲爱的
Lucas, honey?
你和卢卡斯回屋里去 别出来 好吗
You and Lucas get back to the house and stay there, okay?
彼得的自行车
Peter's bike.
你们到底是谁
Who are you?
放下枪 杰克
Put the gun down, Jake.
你怎么知道它在那
How did you know that was there?
发生了什么
What happened?
你和比尔杀了彼得
You and Bill killed Peter,
把尸体扔进湖里 然后埋了自行车
drowned him in the lake, and then buried the bike?
你掩埋不了真相 杰克
You can't bury the truth, Jake.
纸包不住火
Nothing stays buried.
去你的房间呆着 亲爱的
Go to your room, sweetie.
现在就去
Now.
锁上门等着我 不要出来
Lock the door and wait for me. Don't come out.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
35年前 你和比尔杀了彼得·斯威尼
You and Bill killed Peter Sweeney 35 years ago.
这就是我要说的
that's what the hell I'm talking about.
爸爸
Dad.
现在你要面对一个愤怒发狂的鬼魂
And now you got one seriously pissed-off spirit.
它会杀了安德里亚
It's gonna take Andrea,
卢卡斯
Lucas,
你爱的每一个人
everyone you love.
它会把他们淹死
It's gonna drown them,
把他们拖到谁也找不到的地方
and it's gonna drag their bodies god knows where.
你就可以感受到彼得的妈妈所遭受的痛苦
So you can feel the Same pain Peter's mom felt.
之后
And then after that,
它会杀掉你
it's gonna take you,
未达目的前 它不会罢休
and it's not gonna stop until it does.
你怎么知道
How do you know that?
因为这就是它对比尔·卡尔顿所做的一切
Because that's exactly what it did to Bill Carlton.
听听你们都说了些什么
Listen to yourselves,
你们两个
both of you.
你们都疯了
You're insane.
我根本不在乎你对我们的看法
I don't really give a rat's ass what you think of us,
但是如果我们要干掉这个鬼魂
but if we're gonna bring down this spirit,
我们就得找到尸体
we need to find the remains,
给它撒上盐
salt them,
然后把它烧成灰
and burn them into dust.
告诉我 你把彼得埋在哪里了
Tell me you buried Peter somewhere.
别说你就是把它扔进了湖里
Tell me you didn't just let him go in the lake.
来和我玩
Come play with me.
爸爸
Dad,
他们说的都是真的吗
is any of this true?
不 别听他们的
No. Don't listen to them.
他们是骗子 而且很危险
They're liars, and they're dangerous.
有东西想要淹死我
something tried to drown me.
克里斯死在了那个湖里
Chris died on that lake.
爸爸 看着我
Dad, look at me.
告诉我
Tell me.
你没有杀人
you didn't kill anyone.
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
比利和我当时在湖边
Billy and I were at the lake.
彼得个子最小 我们总是欺负他
Peter was the smallest one. We always bullied him,
但那一次
but this time…
不幸发生了
It got rough.
我们把他的头按在水里
We were holding his head under the water.
我们不是故意的
We didn't mean to,
但是我们按得太久了
but we held him under too long,
他淹死了
and he drowned.
我们把尸体进湖里
We let the body go,
它就沉下去了
and it sank.
安德里亚
Oh, Andrea.
我们当时只是孩子
We were kids.
我们怕得要死
We were so scared.
那是个意外
It was a mistake,
但是 安德里亚
but, Andrea,
说我跟这些溺水的人有关
to say that I have anything to do with these drownings,
跟克里斯有关
with Chris,
就因为什么鬼魂
because of some ghost.
那太不理性了
it's not rational.
好吧 听我说
All right, listen to me,
你们家所有人
all of you.
我们得立刻带你们离开这个湖
We need to get you away from this lake.
能走多远走多远
as far as we can right now.
卢卡斯
Lucas!
来和我玩
Come play with me.
卢卡斯
Lucas!
卢卡斯 呆在那别动
Lucas! Stay where you are!
天哪
Oh, my god!
安德里亚呆在那
Andrea, stay there.
不 卢卡斯
No, Lucas!
我们会找到他的 呆在码头上
We'll get him. Stay on the dock.
卢卡斯
Lucas?
萨姆
Sam?
卢卡斯 你在哪
Lucas, where are you?
彼得
Peter,
如果你能听见我
If you can hear me,
求你了 彼得
please, Peter,
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 我非常 - 爸爸 不
- I'm so… - Dad, no!
我非常抱歉
I'm so sorry.
彼得
Peter.
卢卡斯
Lucas.
他只是个小孩子
He's j… he's just a little boy.
求你了 那不是他的错 都是我的错
Please, it's not his fault. It's mine.
带我走吧
Please take me!
杰克
Jake,
不要
No!
听着 让一切都结束吧
Listen, let it be over!
爸爸
Dad.
Daddy!
不
No.
No…
我们不可能救每一个人
Look, we're not gonna save everybody.
我知道
I know.
萨姆
Sam,
迪恩
Dean.
很高兴你们还没走
We're glad we caught you.
我们做了路上吃的午餐给你们
We just, um, we made you lunch for the road.
卢卡斯一定要亲自做三明治
Lucas insisted on making the sandwiches himself.
我能把东西给他们吗
Can I give it to them now?
可以了
Of course.
来 卢卡斯 我们把这个放到车上
Come on, Lucas, let's load this in the car.
你还好吧
How you holding up?
这需要很长一段时间
It's just gonna take a long.
来忘记这事情
time to sort through everything, you know?
安德里亚 对不起
Andrea, I'm sorry.
你们救了我儿子
You saved my son.
我不能要求更多了
I can't ask for more than that.
爸爸很爱我
Dad loved me.
他很爱卢卡斯
He loved Lucas.
不管他做了什么
No matter what he did,
我只能
I just have to…
这么想
hold on to that.
好了
All right,
如果你现在又开始讲话了
if you're gonna be talking now,
这是句很重要的短语
this is a very important phrase,
所以我想让你再重复一遍
so I want you to repeat it one more time.
柏林飞艇 最牛
Zeppelin rules!
好样的 击掌
That's right. Up high.
好好照顾你妈妈 好吗
Take care of your mom, okay?
谢谢你
Thank you.
萨姆 走吧
Sam, move your ass.
再不走天就黑了
We're gonna run out of daylight before we hit the road.